<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://docs.cattheme.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://docs.cattheme.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-09-28T21:03:11+08:00</updated><id>http://docs.cattheme.com/</id><title type="html">Cattheme Docs</title><subtitle>Cattheme.com Document.</subtitle><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><entry><title type="html">Rabel</title><link href="http://docs.cattheme.com/themes/rabel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rabel" /><published>2017-06-18T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2017-06-18T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://docs.cattheme.com/themes/rabel</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://docs.cattheme.com/themes/rabel/">&lt;p&gt;Thanks for purchase Rabel Magento2 responsive theme, this guide will help you to install and use this great theme in your site, if you have further questions please contact us at gizmocn@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-how-to-install&quot;&gt;1. How to install&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Except theme files package, we also provide a quickstart package, the quickstart package should be installed as test site to learn theme’s setting and featured, please
don’t use quickstart for live site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;11-theme-installation&quot;&gt;1.1 Theme installation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Theme installation is after Magento 2.x installation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After your Magento 2.x is ready(new Magento installtion or existed Magento 2.x site), you can start to install Rabel theme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Backup your Magento 2.x site(All files, folders and database).&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;warning&quot;&gt;Warning: We strongly recommend you to backup all files, folders and database before upload theme file&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Theme files upload&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Unzip Rabel Theme &amp;gt; rabel_theme.zip  and upload all directories(Therea are 2 directories - app, pub) to Magento 2.x root directory.
you can use ftp sftp or cpanel to do this.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Active Cattheme Theme and Extensions.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Open command line in Magneto root folder. and run below Magneto command:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;language-bash highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;$ &lt;/span&gt;php bin/magento setup:upgrade
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Select Rabel Theme in Magneto Backend&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Lgoin Magento backend and goes to  Content -&amp;gt; Design -&amp;gt; Configuration  then select the Store View you want to applied this theme and then click Edit link.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Select Applied Theme to Cattheme Rabel Default,  and then click Save Configuration button, see below picture:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/applied_theme.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Applied Theme&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Demo Installation&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;In Magento Backend, goes to Cattheme -&amp;gt;  Cattheme Theme Install -&amp;gt; Theme Install.  There are 3 options for here:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Select Demo to Import: Select the demo you want to import.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Overwrite Existing Blocks and Pages: If you want to overwrite existing same id Blocks and Pages, select Yes or No.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Configuration Scope: Select store you want to applied this demo.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;See below picture for a example:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/demo_installation.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Demo Installation&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;After you selected all options, click Import Configuration Button and now refresh your website frontend and select storeview you applied this theme, the demo will
 be installed.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;notice&quot;&gt;Notice: If you encounter &quot;can not save configuration file&quot; error, it mostly is caused by folder or file owner and permission, please refer
     Magento official guide to change owner or permission &lt;a href=&quot;http://devdocs.magento.com/guides/v2.1/install-gde/install-quick-ref.html&quot;&gt;http://devdocs.magento.com/guides/v2.1/install-gde/install-quick-ref.html&lt;/a&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;12-quickstart-installation&quot;&gt;1.2 Quickstart Installation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-theme-configuration&quot;&gt;2. Theme Configuration&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most theme configuration can be found at &lt;Magento Backend=&quot;&quot;&gt;-&amp;gt;CATTHEME-&amp;gt;Rabel Theme Config&lt;/Magento&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/rabel_theme_configuration.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rabel Theme Configuration&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All configurations are listed by several sections:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/configurations_listing.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Configuration Listing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many options in these sections, you can input color value, select header type or input header height etc to the options, before we start to discuss all options, please remember,
after you complete options selection, don’t forget to click “Save Config” button to store your selections to database.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/save_config.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Save Config&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now we will discuss details of all there configurations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-font&quot;&gt;3. Font&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Font options will show when you select Custom Option to “Yes”
In this sections, we divide all font configurations to 6 groups, they are body font, Element Font 1 to Element Font 5&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;31-body-font&quot;&gt;3.1 Body Font&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/theme_font_customization.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Theme Font Customization&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Body font is global setting for entire website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Body Font Size: select body font size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Body Font Weight: input body font weight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Body Font Style: select body font style.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Body Font Family: you can select system general fonts, or google font, when you select google font option, a new option “Body Font Family - Google Fonts” will appear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Body Font Family - Google Fonts: you can select google font, after you select a google font, the font preview will be showed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See below picture for a example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/body_font_custom.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Body Font Customization&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Select “Eagle Lake” google font for body and then click “Save Config” button in backend top right corner, now refresh your store frontend and you can find the site font was changed according your selecation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/body_font_effect.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Body Font Effect&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;32-element-font-1---element-font-5&quot;&gt;3.2 Element Font 1 - Element Font 5&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Element Font, we can customize font for specific html element, For example, we want change font family for product name of category and product page, 
First, we need to find css class or ID of product name by using  browser development tools(Firefox or Chrome).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Firefox, we find class for product name of 
category page is ‘.prodduct-item-link’ (don’t forget add “.” for css class and “#” for id).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/product_name_css_element.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Product Name class for category page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And class for product name of product page is ‘.product-content-wrapper .page-title’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/product_name_css_class.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Product Name class for product page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we have Font Element 1 options like below picture:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/element_font.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Element Font Setting&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we only change font-family and leave element font size, weight and style to theirs default value, 
So in website frontend, product name style will inherit font size, weight and style setting from theme and only font family is changed to
 “petit Formal Script”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/product_name_font_in_category.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Product Name in Category Page&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/product_name_font.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Product Name in Product Page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have 5 Element Font options group, so you can different html element to different font family, size weight and style.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-color&quot;&gt;4. Color&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this section, we have “predefined Color Scheme” options, you can select different color scheme, if you are not satisfied with default or predefined 
color, you can select “custom” options to “yes”, and input your color for different area of the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/color_setting.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Color Setting&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After set “custom” option to “yes”, all color input options will be appear, color options are divided into groups (General, Header, Megamenu 
Category Page, Newsletter Popup, Before Footer, Footer).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to color for a option, just click text input field, a color picker will be
showed, now select the color from picker, of course, if you already have hex color code, just input the code directly to the text input field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/color_picker.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Color Picker&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you complete all you color options, don’t forget to click “Save Config” button to save your choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-general&quot;&gt;5. General&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This sections, we can select different site layout (boxed or full width) and site’s background image or pattern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/general_section.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;General Section&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please see below picture for difference between full width, boxed layout 1 and boxed layout2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/layout.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Site Layout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6-header-type&quot;&gt;6. Header Type&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this sections, you can select different header and every header has different options like padding and height, some header type has options 
to add static block to header.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below pictures show different header:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Header Type 1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/header1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Header Type 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Header Type 2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/header2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Header Type 2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Header Type 3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/header3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Header Type 3&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Header Type 4&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/header4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Header Type 4&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Header Type 5 is almost same as header type 2, just in homepage, the header will overlap with slider show&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/header5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Header Type 5&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Header Type 6 is almost same as header type 3, just in homepage, the header will overlap with slider show&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/header6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Header Type 6&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Header Type 7 is almost same as header type 2, the only difference is the header is full width.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-megamenu-configuration&quot;&gt;7. Megamenu Configuration&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This section options will coordinate with Categories Mega Menu options(Backend -&amp;gt; Products -&amp;gt; Categories -&amp;gt; Mega Menu) to configure Mega menu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Megamenu Configuration Section(Backend -&amp;gt; Cattheme -&amp;gt; Rabel Theme Config -&amp;gt; Megamenu Configuration) is for general Megamenu setting:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/megamenu_section.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Megamenu Configuration&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Magemenu Options in Categories (Backend -&amp;gt; Products -&amp;gt; Categories -&amp;gt; Mega Menu) is for dedicated category:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/megamenu.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Megamenu for dedicated category&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s discuss Megamenu Configuration Secion First.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;71-megamenu-configuration-section&quot;&gt;7.1 Megamenu Configuration Section&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;711-general-group&quot;&gt;7.1.1 General Group&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) General - Enable Megamenu: Enable or disable the megamenu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) General - Enable Home Link: Enable or disable Home Link.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) General - Enable Sticky Menu: Enable or disable sticky menu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) General - Sticky Menu Logo: You can add a logo for sticky menu, it is only work for some of header type.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) General - Enable full width dropdown: Enable or disable full width dropdown. Below pictures show the difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/full_width_dropdown.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Enable Full Width Dropdown&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/disable_full_width_dropdown.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Disable Full Width Dropdown&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;712-thumbnail-image-setting&quot;&gt;7.1.2 Thumbnail Image Setting&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Categories Level definition is shown as follow:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/categories_level.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Categories Level&quot; /&gt;
The specific category thumbnail is upload at (Backend -&amp;gt; Products -&amp;gt; Categories -&amp;gt; Mega Menu -&amp;gt; Item Thumbnail). Here we just set if show 
categories thumbnail for level1 and level2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Thumbnail Image Setting - If show level 1 categroy thumbnail image: show or not level 1 category thumbnail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Thumbnail Image Setting - If show level 2 categroy thumbnail image: show or not level 2 category thumbnail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Thumbnail Image Setting - Select level 2 category thumbnail image position: select level2 category thumbnail image position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See below pictures for examples to show  level1 category thumbnial:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eample 1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/category_thumbnail.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Categories Thumbnail Example&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example 2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/another_category_thumbnail.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Another Categories Thumbnail Example&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;713-custom-menu-setting&quot;&gt;7.1.3 Custom Menu Setting&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to add custom menu please set “Enable Custom Link” to Yes, Once you set this option to “Yes”, more options will be appeared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Custom Menu Setting - Enable Custom Link: Enable or disble custom link or dropdown feature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Custom Menu Setting - Select Custom Link: Select custom links to show in main navigation, this is mulit-select box, if you want to select multi items,
hold “ctrl” in keyboard and click mouse left button.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Before something showed in this multi-select box, you need  add custom link or custom dropdown in Backend -&amp;gt; Content -&amp;gt; Blocks, add blocks with 
identifier begin with ctmenu_ or ctmenu_block_ .&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To add custom menu with link, add static block with identifier begin with ctmenu_ .
    &lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt; Block Title =&amp;gt; as menu title.
 Menu identifier =&amp;gt; as menu url link last part.
 Block =&amp;gt; ignore. 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To add custom menu without link but with dropdown, add static block with idetifier begin with ctmenu_block_.
    &lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt; Block Title =&amp;gt; as menu title.
 Menu identifier =&amp;gt; ignore
 Block =&amp;gt; as custom menu dropdown
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See below picture for a example, we selected two items for “Select Custom Link” option:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/custom_menu.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Custom Link Dropdown Setting&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After clicked “Save Config” button in top right corner, in you browser to check your website, both “Home Design” and About Us has shown in main
navigation and as both menu itmes block identifier is begin with ctmenu_block_ , so both custom menu items will show content as dropdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/custom_link_dropdown.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Custom Link Dropdown Effect&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Custom Menu Setting - Change Custom Menu Order： Setting mutl custom item order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s see a example, if you don’t set menu order, the custom menu order is from top to bottom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backend Setting
&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/custom_menu_default.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Custom Menu Default Order&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frontend Effect:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/frontend_default.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Custom Menu Default Order Frontend&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now We set “Change Custom Menu Order” to “2,1,3”, and you can see the different:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backend Setting
&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/custom_menu_order.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Custom Menu Change Order&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frontend Effect:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/custom_menu_order_effect.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Custom Menu Change Order Frontend&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;72-magemenu-options-in-categories&quot;&gt;7.2 Magemenu Options in Categories&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now we start to discuss Megamenu options for in Categories, if you want to configure specific category, please go Backend -&amp;gt; Products -&amp;gt; Categories, then 
select category, and then select Mega Menu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/megamenu_in_categories.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Magemenu Options in Categories&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, We will discuss all this options usage one by one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Mega Menu - Menu Type: select menu type, Vertical layout and Horizontal layout, see below picture for different of these two type menu type.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/vertical_megamenu.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Vertical Megamenu Layout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/horizontal_megamenu.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Horizontal Megamenu Layout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Mega Menu - Featured Image: if you want to show a image in megamenu for this cateogry, upload the image here, refer to &lt;a href=&quot;#712-thumbnail-image-setting&quot;&gt;7.1.2 Thumbnail Image Setting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;NOTE&lt;/em&gt;: Magento 2.1.0 to Magento 2.1.7 has some issue to upload extra category image, the issue is solved in Magento 2.1.8. For Magento 2.1.0 to 2.1.7, you need to apply patch 
in order to upload featured image, details is &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/magento/magento2/pull/5978/commits/70d3468b24ffbbd4233123c8d60916a440975b39&quot;&gt;github: category attribute image issue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Mega Menu - Top Block: Select static block that appeared in top area of megamenu, This field is applicable for level 0 categories only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Mega Menu - Left Block: Select static block that appeared in left side of megamenu, This field is applicable for level 0 categories only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Mega Menu - Right Block Block: Select static block that appeared in right side of megamenu, This field is applicable for level 0 categories only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Mega Menu - Bottom Block: Select static block that appeared in bottom area of megamenu, This field is applicable for level 0 categories only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Mega Menu - Left Block Width: This field is applicable for level 0 categories only. NOTE : Total of “Left Block”, “Category Block Width” and “Right Block Width” must be equal to 12, not more or less than 12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) Mega Menu - Right Block Width: This field is applicable for level 0 categories only. NOTE : Total of “Left Block”, “Category Block Width” and “Right Block Width” must be equal to 12, not more or less than 12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Mega Menu - Category Width: This field is applicable for level 0 categories only. NOTE : Total of “Left Block”, “Category Block Width” and “Right Block Width” must be equal to 12, not more or less than 12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10) Mega Menu - Category Column: Set megamenu dropdown category columns, this field is applicable for level 0 categories only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below picture show the meaning of Mega Menu 3-9 options:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Megamenu Backend Confugurations:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/megamenu_blocks_backend.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Megamenu Backend Configuration&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Megamenu Frontend Effect:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/megamenu_and_blocks.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Megamenu Frontend Effect&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11) Mega Menu - Category Label: Input Category Label text content, for example “New”, “Hot!”, “Sale!”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12) Mega Menu - Category Label Background Color: Input category label background color. Example “#ff0000”, “#ffff00”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below picture show example of category label:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/category_label_example.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Category Label Example&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;8-product-label&quot;&gt;8. Product Label&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This section set “New” and “Sale” label for proruct item in category and product page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Product Label - Show New Product Label: Enable or disable “New” label.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you set this options to “yes”, then products with “Set Product As New From”, “Set Product As New To(This date will be in the future)”  options setting in backend product edit page will has “New” label in frontend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/set_product_new.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;New Label&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Product Label - New Label Text: Set New label text, default is “New”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Product Label - Show Sales Product Label: Enable or disable “Sale” Label.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In backend product edit page, click “Advanced Pricing” link for Price option, will open a Advanced pricing popup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/advanced_pricing.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Advanced Pricing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you set ‘Product Label - Show Sales Product Label’ to ‘Yes’, and in the same time, you set ‘Special Price’, ‘Special Price From’ and 
‘Special Price To(the future date)’ options in Advanced Pricing Popup, the “Sale” label will be appeared for this prodcut in frontend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/set_sale_label.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sale Label&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Product Label - Sale Label Text: Set Sale label text, default is “Sale”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Product Label - Replace sales text with discount rate: If set to yes, Sales label will replace by discount percent rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Product Label example in category page:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/product_label_example.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Product labe in category page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Product Label example in product page:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/product_label_for_product_details.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Product labe in product page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;9-category-page&quot;&gt;9. Category Page&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;91-general&quot;&gt;9.1 General&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This section is options for category page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) General - If show hero in category page: Enable or disable hero title for category page, if you select “Yes”, more options will be appeared and full width hero title will be show for categories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) General - Category Hero Default Image:  Upload default picture for all categories, of course,  you can upload unique picture for specific category in backend cateogry manage page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/hero_image.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Upload Uniqie Image For a Category&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) General - Category Hero Title Height: Input height of Hero title.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) General - Enable Parallax For Hero Title: Enable or disalbe parallax effect for hero title.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See below for the different of hero title was enabled or disabled:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enable Hero Title:
&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/enable_hero_title.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Enable Hero Title&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disable Hero Title
&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/disable_hero_title.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Disable Hero Title&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;92-category-grid-setting&quot;&gt;9.2 Category Grid Setting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Category Grid Setting - Select Category Style: Select different category style.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See pictures below for screen capture for all category style:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/category_style1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Category Style 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/category_style2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Category Style 2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/category_style3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Category Style 3&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/category_style4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Category Style 4&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/category_style5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Category Style 5&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/category_style6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Category Style 6&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Category Grid Setting - Select Mobile Category Style: Select different category style for mobile devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See pictures below for screen capture for all mobile category style:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/mobile_category_style1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mobile Category Style 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/mobile_category_style2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mobile Category Style 2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Category Grid Setting - Move Add to cart and add to buttons to image area: If move add to cart and add to buttons to image area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See pictures below for details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Move Buttons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/move_buttons.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Move Buttons&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not Move Buttons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/no_move_buttons.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Not Move Button&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Category Grid Setting - Columns Per Row: Setting product columns in desktop PC, the columns for tablet and mobile will adjust automatically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Category Grid Setting - Show Alternative Image When Hover: If show alternative image when hover if the product has 2 or more pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Category Grid Setting - Show Review: if show review.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Category Grid Setting - Show Wishlist and Compare buttons: If show wishlist and compare buttons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) Category Grid Setting - Keep Image Aspect Ratio: if keep image aspect ratio. if you set this option to “no”, Image Height option will be appeared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Category Grid Setting - Image Width: Input product picture width, default is 300.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Category Grid Setting - Image Height: Input product picture height, default is 300. this option is only appeared when ‘Keep Image Aspect Ratio’ is ‘no’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;10-product-view-page&quot;&gt;10. Product View Page&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This section is for product details apge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Product View Page - Gallery Width: Select Gallery width, Gallery and product info total width is 12, for example, if you select gallery width to 7, then
product info width will be set to 5 automatically, see below picture for details:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/gallery_width.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Gallery Width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Product View Page - Enable vertical thumbnails: Enable or disable vertical thumbnails. See below picture for frontend example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eanble vertical thumbnail:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/vertical_thumbnails.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Enable vertical thumbnail&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Product View Page - Enable Product Picture Zoom: Enable or disable product picture zoom effect. If enable product zoom, when mouse hover on
product picture, zooom effect will be trigger, see below picture for details:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/gallery_zoom.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Enable product picture zoom&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Product View Page - Enable Full Width Tabs Layout: Enable or disable full width tabs layout, see below pictures for different for layouts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Generall Tabs Layout:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/general_tabs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;General Tabs Layout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full Width Tabs Layout:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/full_width_tabs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Full Width Tabs Layout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Product View Page - Input your social code: Input your social code copied from addthis.com or other sites, or leave it empty to disable this feature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social code example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/icon_share_feature.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Social Code Example&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frontend Socail Button position:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/social_buttons.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Frontend social buttons position&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;11-newsletter-popup&quot;&gt;11. Newsletter Popup&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This section configure homepage newsletter popup feature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Newsletter popup - Enable: Enable or disable homepage newsletter popup, if you set this option to “yes”, more options for newsletter popup will be appeared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Newsletter pupup - Popup expires end: Set period in days after which popup will be shown again if customer has already subscribed or chosen option Don’t show this popup again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Newsletter popup - Newsletter Logo: If you want to show logo in newsletter popup, please upload logo here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Newsletter popup - Popup Content Text: Input newsletter popup content text here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Newsletter popup - Newsletter Popup Width: Input newsletter popup width: for example 500, default is 600.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Newsletter popup - Newsletter Popup Height: Input newsletter popup height: for example 500, default is 450.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Newsletter popup - Popup Background Image: Upload newsletter popup background image.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below pictures show Newsletter popup backend configuration and appearance of frontend, you can compare theme and get to know the meaning of some options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Newsletter Popup Background Configurations:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/newsletter_backend.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Newsletter Popup Background Configuratons&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Newsletter Popups Frontend Appearance:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/newsletter_frontend.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Newsletter Popup Frontend Appearance&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;12-before-footer&quot;&gt;12. Before Footer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This section is simple, only two options:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Before Footer - Enable: Enable or disable before footer, if you set this option to “yes”, new option will be appeared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Before Footer - Select Static Block for Before Footer: Select a static block for before footer. see below picture for the example of before footer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/before_footer.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Before Footer&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;13-footer&quot;&gt;13. Footer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This section is for footer of the site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to understand footer options meaning, please see below picture for footer layout:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/footer_layout.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Footer Layout&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Footer consists of footer first row, second row and footer bottom, you can put 1-4 static blocks for first row and second row respectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Footer - Custom Css class for footer: Add a unique CSS class for footer area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Footer - Static Block for Column 1: Select static block for first row column 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Footer - Column 1 Width: Select Column 1 width, total width for first row is 12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Footer - Static Block for Column 2: Select static block for first row column 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Footer - Column 2 Width: Select Column 2 width, total width for first row is 12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Footer - Static Block for Column 3: Select static block for first row column 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Footer - Column 3 Width: Select Column 3 width, total width for first row is 12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) Footer - Static Block for Column 4: Select static block for first row column 4.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Footer - Column 4 Width: Select Column 4 width, total width for first row is 12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10) Footer - Enable Second Row: Enable or disable footer second row, if you select “yes” for this option, more options for second row will
be appeared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11) Footer - Static Block for Second Row Column 1: Select static block for second row column 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12) Footer - Second Row Column 1 Width: Select Second Row Column 1 width, total width for second row is 12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13) Footer - Static Block for Second Row Column 1: Select static block for second row column 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;14) Footer - Second Row Column 2 Width: Select Second Row Column 2 width, total width for second row is 12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;15) Footer - Static Block for Second Row Column 1: Select static block for second row column 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;16) Footer - Second Row Column 3 Width: Select Second Row Column 3 width, total width for second row is 12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;17) Footer - Static Block for Second Row Column 1: Select static block for second row column 4.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18) Footer - Second Row Column 4 Width: Select Second Row Column 4 width, total width for second row is 12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;19) Footer - Show Store Switcher: Enable or disable store switcher, for multi-store site, if set this option to “yes”, a store switch will 
be appeared in footer bottom area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20) Footer - Footer Logo: If you want to show a logo in footer area, please upload logo here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;14-recent-blog-post-widget-setting&quot;&gt;14. Recent Blog Post Widget Setting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This section is for recent blog post widget, you need to add the recent blog post widget first(Refer to &lt;a href=&quot;#167-recent-blog-posts-widget&quot;&gt;16.7 Recent Blog Posts Widget&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Recent Blog Post Widget Setting - If show background image: If show background image, if you set this option to “Yes”, more options will
be appeared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Recent Blog Post Widget Setting - Background Image: upload background image for this widget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Recent Blog Post Widget Setting - Background Repeat: set background repeat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Recent Blog Post Widget Setting - Background Size: set background size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Recent Blog Post Widget Setting - If show featured image for every post: if show featured image for posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Recent Blog Post Widget Setting - If show short content for every post: if show short content for posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;15-custom-css-and-module-installed&quot;&gt;15. Custom Css and Module Installed&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;custom-css&quot;&gt;Custom Css&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can add custom Css in “Add Custom Css” textarea, or add to file “app/design/frontend/Cattheme/rabel/web/css/custom.css”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;module-installed&quot;&gt;Module Installed&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can see all module and its version that come with our theme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;16-widgets&quot;&gt;16. Widgets&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our theme, we add several widgets to let you insert content easily, for how to use Magento widget, please refer official user guide. 
If you want to insert widget to CMS page or block, please refer &lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.magento.com/m2/ce/user_guide/cms/editor-widget.html&quot;&gt;Inserting a Widget&lt;/a&gt;, or you 
can insert widget from Backend-&amp;gt; Content -&amp;gt; Widgets, refer official guide &lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.magento.com/m2/ce/user_guide/cms/widget-create.html&quot;&gt;Creating a Widget&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;161-cattheme-brands-list-widget&quot;&gt;16.1 Cattheme Brands List Widget&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This widget will show brands logo in frontend, when you click the logo, it will go to the brand product search page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/brands_list.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Brands List Widget&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to use this wiget, you first have to prepare brands logo, you can use gif png or jpg format and logo’s named as brands name,  just use lowercase and “_”, for example: if brand name is 
RABEL, the image name should be rabel.gif( or rabel.png, rabel.jpg), another example: River Bridge is your brand name, so the image name will be river_bridge.gif (or river_bridge.png, river_bridge.jpg), 
all logo must be same image format.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you completed all logo image, upload all logos image to folder &lt;your Magento=&quot;&quot; root=&quot;&quot;&gt;/pub/media/cattheme/rabel/brands.&lt;/your&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now go to Magento backend-&amp;gt; STORES -&amp;gt; Attributes -&amp;gt; Product, select Manufacturer attribute, In Manage Options(Values of Your Attribute), add options like below picture:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/manufacturer_attribute.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Manufacturer Attribute&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: Value for Default Store View should be brand name, for example your brand is River Bridge, input “River Bridge” for Default Store View, the widget will convert this name to river_bridge and load relative logo image.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can add widget now, check below simple widget configuration:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/brandslist_widget.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Brands List Widget&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Brands: select brands you want to show in frontend, Hold down ctrl and then use mouse to select multi-brands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Title: Widget Title.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) If link to brands’ products: if you store have products with manufacturer attribute, you can set this option to “yes”, so when you click the brand logo, it will go to this brand search page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Link to new window or not: select if open new window or not when click brand logo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Image Format: your logo image format.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;162-cattheme-cms-layout-widget&quot;&gt;16.2 Cattheme CMS Layout Widget&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By using this widget, you can put one or multiple static block in one row to frontend. Let’s discuss this widget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below picture show options for this widget:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/cms_layout_widget.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;CMS Layout Widget&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Layout: You can put several blocks in one row, we have some examples for the meaning of the options:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/4 + 1/4 + 1/4 + 1/4: Put 4 blocks in one row, and every row has 1/4 (25%) width.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/4 + 1/4 + 2/4: put 3 blocks in one row, first and second blocks occupy 25%(1/4) width, the third block has 50%(2/4) width.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/1: put 1 block in one row, this block occupy 100% width.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/2 + 1/2: pub 2 blocks in one row, every block has 50% width.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) to 5): Select blocks to show, if you select 4 blocks layout, you need to select all 4 options, if you layout is only need 2 blocks, just select Area 1 and Area 2 blocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) If include Bootstrap container class in layout: if include bootstrap container class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Custom Css class: Add unique custom css class for this widget&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;163-cattheme-categroy-list-widget&quot;&gt;16.3 Cattheme Categroy List Widget&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By using this widget, you can put selected categoreis in website frontend, the widget options is discussed as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/category_list_widget.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Category List Widget&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Widget Title: This title will be showed as header of widget block, Empty to disable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Choose Categories: Choose one or several categories to show in frontend, hold down “Ctrl” key, you can select multiple category by click mouse left button.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) If display category image: if show category image, here the image is the one upload in Megamenu tab of backend category page, see below picture for details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/category_list_widget_image.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Category List Widget Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Image Width: Category image width, for example 250, default is 150.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Image Height: Category image height, for example 250, default is 150.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Show total number of products: if show number of products in the category.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Columns per row: Columns of categories per row, default is 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;164-cattheme-google-map-widget&quot;&gt;16.4 Cattheme Google Map Widget&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can use this widget to insert google map in everywhere of you website, the below picture show the options of this widget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/google_map_widget.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Google Map Widget&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The options are self-explanatory, you can easily to input value for these options according our widget configuration example picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;165-cattheme-owl-slider-widget&quot;&gt;16.5 Cattheme Owl Slider Widget&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This widget has only one option, just select the slider you want to show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;166-cattheme-products-list-widget&quot;&gt;16.6 Cattheme Products List Widget&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use this widget to show latest, bestseller, popular product etc to everywhere in your website. Below picture show the options of this widget:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/product_list_widget.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Product List Widget&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All options of this widget will discuss as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Title: Widget Title.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Product Type&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Latest Products (Show products that you import to site most recently)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;New Products(Show products that have “Set Product As New From” and “Set Products as New To” defined in backend product page)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Special Products(Show products with special price)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Popular Products(Most view products)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Bestsell Products(Best Sell products)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Top Rated Products(Top rated products)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Random Products&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Featured Products(Show products that have “Is Featured” to “Yes” in backend product page)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Deal Products(Show product that have special price and have “Special Price From” and “Special Price To” setting. If you select “Deal Products”,
a deal countdown will be appeared in frontend, see below pictures for details.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/special_price_countdown.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Product Deal Template&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;if you set Product Type to “Deal Products” and Template to “Product Deal Template”, special price countdown will has different style, see below picture for details&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/product_deal_template.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Special Price Countdown&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Number of Products to Show: Set total products to show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Number of Columns: Set products columns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Tempalte: Select tempalte.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Product Grid Style: This option is only work for Product Grid Template, Please select product widget grid style, If you do not select this, 
   the Style will be same as Category Grid Style, for appearance of every grid style, please refer to &lt;a href=&quot;#92-category-grid-setting&quot;&gt;9.2 Category Grid Setting&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Display Page Control: Enable or disable Page Control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;167-recent-blog-posts-widget&quot;&gt;16.7 Recent Blog Posts Widget&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use this widget to show recent blog post in every where of your website, let’s discuss all options of this widget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Title: Please specify title you want to display on the frontend. You can leave it blank if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Number of Posts: Please indicate number of recent posts you want to display. Leave blank to use predefined “Posts Per Page” value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Blog Category: Leave blank to display posts from all categories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Custom Template: Leave blank to use default template Magefan_Blog::widget/recent.phtml. Magefan_Blog::widget/recent_masonry.phtml template is also available out of the box.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note&lt;/em&gt;: There are extra setting for recent blog posts widget in system configuration, please refer to &lt;a href=&quot;#14-recent-blog-post-widget-setting&quot;&gt;14. Recent Blog Post Widget Setting&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;17-other-modules&quot;&gt;17. Other Modules&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;171-cattheme-owlslider-module&quot;&gt;17.1 Cattheme OwlSlider Module&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;1711-manage-sliders&quot;&gt;17.1.1 Manage Sliders&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OwlSlider Module can add slider to homepage or other page, we use this module to add homepage slider for every demo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new slider, go to Magento Backend -&amp;gt; CATTHEME -&amp;gt; Cattheme OwlSlider&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/cattheme_owlslider_module.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cattheme OwlSlider Module&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here, you can find Manage Sliders and Manage Banners, First we need to add a slider and then add any number banners to the slider you just added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click Manage Sliders and open sliders list window, it list all sliders for the store,　click “Add New Slider” button to add new slider, click “select” to edit or delete existed slider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/sliders_list_window.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;OwlSlider Moduel Sliders List Window&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We now try to add a new slider, so click “Add New Slider” button, open slider edit window:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/add_new_slider.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Add New Slider&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The options meaning is explained as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Title: Slider Name.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Identifier: Slider unique ID string.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Slider Status: Enable or disable the slider.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Layout: Select from “Full Width”, “Full Screen”　or “Fixed Width”.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Slider Height: For “Full Width” and “Fxied Width” Layout, you need to input slider height.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Animate In: Select effect when background image enter view.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Animate Out: Select effect when background iamge leave view.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Autoplay: Enable or disabel autoplay.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pause on mouse hover: Enable or disable pause when mouse hover.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Autoplay speed: Input autoplay speed, default is 3000, meaning switch banners per every 3 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Loop: Enable or disable loop.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Show next and prev navigation: Show or hide next/prev navigation button.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Show paging navigation: Show or hide paging navigation(dot).&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;notice&quot;&gt;
      Note: if ignore both animate in and animateout options, the banner switch effect is slider in and slider out.
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After fill all options, Click “Save Slider” button and then return to sliders list window, now record the ID and Title of the slider you just added, we will need this ID when adding the slider to web page and we 
will need  the Title when assigning banners to the slider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/remember_slider_id.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Remember Slider ID&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;1712-manage-banners&quot;&gt;17.1.2 Manage Banners&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After add a slider, now we can use “Manage Banners” to assign banners to the slider, click Magento Bankend -&amp;gt; CATTHEME -&amp;gt; Manage Banners, banners list window will be opened:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/banners_list_window.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Banners List Window&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In banners list window, you can add new banners, edit or delete existed banners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now we will add new banner, so click “Add New Banner” button, then open banner edit window:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/add_new_banners.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Add a New Banner&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The options in this window is explained as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Status: Enable or disabel the banner.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Assigned to Slider: This select box will list all Slider Title, select the slider that you want to assign this banner to.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Order: You can assign any number banners to a slider, here input the order of current banner, for example 0, 1 etc.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Banner Content Add banner content here, see note for details.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Banner Image: Select a image to upload as banner background.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Background Color: Input banner background color.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;details-about-banner-conent&quot;&gt;Details about Banner Conent&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We add several predefined class to help to add banner content easily, the Let’s see a typical banner content:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Code:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-bash highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;div &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;slide-content slide-left slide-background&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;  
    &amp;lt;p &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;middle-txt white&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;Nam libero tempore&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;p &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;big-txt white  cursive&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;Excepteur sint occaecat&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;div &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;transparent-btn&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a&amp;gt;Buy it now&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actuall Effect:
&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/banner_content.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Actual Effect of Banner Content&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For div with class slide-content, you can add following class: slide-left, slide-right, slide-middle, content-fadein, slide-background, align-center, top, bottom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For p element inside div.slide-content, you can add following class: white, golden, red, shadow, black, small-txt, mdddle-txt, big-txt, extra-txt, middle-red, small-red.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also add animate effect for p element: slideBounceInDownFast, slideBounceInDownSlow, slideBounceInDownVerySlow, slideFadeIn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For button div: you can add red-btn, transparent-btn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, you can add more class as you wish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;1713-add-slider-to-page&quot;&gt;17.1.3 Add Slider to page&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have several method to add slider to a page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1 add to page’s Layout Update XML:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/add_slider_to_layout_update.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Add Slider to Layout Update XML&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Code:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-bash highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;referenceContainer &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;ctowlslider&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;
      &amp;lt;block &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Cattheme&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;se&quot;&gt;\O&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;wlSlider&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;se&quot;&gt;\B&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;lock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;se&quot;&gt;\W&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;idget&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;se&quot;&gt;\O&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;wlSlider&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;action &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;method&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;setData&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;
         &amp;lt;argument &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;name&quot;&lt;/span&gt; xsi:type&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;string&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;slider_id&amp;lt;/argument&amp;gt;
         &amp;lt;argument &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;value&quot;&lt;/span&gt; xsi:type&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;string&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;7&amp;lt;/argument&amp;gt;
     &amp;lt;/action&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/block&amp;gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;gp&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/referenceContainer&amp;gt; &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2 add to page’s content:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Code:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;

{{block class=&quot;Cattheme\OwlSlider\Block\Widget\OwlSlider&quot; name=&quot;slider6&quot; slider_id=&quot;7&quot;}}

&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 add from widget:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have add a widget named as Cattheme Owl Slider to help to add slider to different area easily. it is simple widget, just one option to select Slide to put to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;172-cattheme-simpletabs-module&quot;&gt;17.2 Cattheme Simpletabs Module&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use this module, you can show multi-categories products in tabs, See below for actuall example of this module:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/cattheme_simpletabs_module.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cattheme Simpletabs Module&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to configure this module click Magento backend -&amp;gt; CATTHEME -&amp;gt; Cattheme Simpletabs -&amp;gt; Simpletabs Config, it will open the module configuration window:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/simpletabs_configuration.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cattheme Simpletabs Module Configuration&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below we give the details of all module configuration options:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;General - Enable Simpletabs: Enable or disable this module.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;General - Title: The module title.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;General - Action to switch tab: Select mouse action to switch tab, you can select “Click” or “Hover”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Product Selection - Select Category: Select categies that will show in frontend of you website, Hold down Ctrl and then you can select multi-categories.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Product Selection - Product Field to Order By: Select product type to show in tabs, You can select from Name, Id, Data Created, Price, Top Rating, Most Reviews, Most Viewed, Most Selling Random.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Product Selection - Ordering Direction: Select ASC or DESC&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Product Selection - Product Limitation: Input number of products to show in every tab.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tabs Options - Categories Order By: Select Tabs order, you can select Random, Name, Id Position.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Tabs Options - Categories Ordering Direction: Select ASC or DESC.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Product Dispaly Setting - If dispaly products image: If show product image.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Product Dispaly Setting - Image Width. Product Width, example 300.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Product Dispaly Setting - Image Height: Product Height, example 300.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you have fill all options, Click “Save Config” to save module configuration. Now you can add the module in you page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can add the module to page’s Layout Update XML or page’s Content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The code to add module at Layout Update XML&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-bash highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;referenceContainer &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;content&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;
   &amp;lt;block &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Cattheme&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;se&quot;&gt;\S&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;impletabs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;se&quot;&gt;\B&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;lock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;se&quot;&gt;\S&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;impletabs&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;simpletabs.theme&quot;&lt;/span&gt; /&amp;gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;gp&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/referenceContainer&amp;gt; &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The code to add module to page’s content:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;

{{block class=&quot;Cattheme\Simpletabs\Block\Simpletabs&quot; name=&quot;simpletabs1&quot; }}

&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, we can also fill more options in the code, this way you can add multi-moduel with different configuration to page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full configuration code for Layout&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-bash highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;referenceContainer &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;content&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;
   &amp;lt;block &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Cattheme&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;se&quot;&gt;\S&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;impletabs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;se&quot;&gt;\B&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;lock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;se&quot;&gt;\S&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;impletabs&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;simpletabs.theme&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Latest Products&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;switch_action&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;click&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;product_category&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;10, 15, 30&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;product_order_by&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;created_at&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;product_order_dir&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;ASC&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;product_limitation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;5&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;categories_order_by&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;position&quot;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;categories_order_dir&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;ASC&quot;&lt;/span&gt; product_image_disp＝&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;yes&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;product_image_width&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;300&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;product_image_height&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;300&quot;&lt;/span&gt; /&amp;gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;gp&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/referenceContainer&amp;gt; &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full configuration code for page’s content&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;

{{block class=&quot;Cattheme\Simpletabs\Block\Simpletabs&quot; name=&quot;simpletabs1&quot; title=&quot;Latest Products&quot; switch_action=&quot;click&quot; product_category=&quot;10, 15, 30&quot; product_order_by=&quot;created_at&quot; product_order_dir=&quot;ASC&quot; product_limitation=&quot;5&quot; categories_order_by=&quot;position&quot;  categories_order_dir=&quot;ASC&quot; product_image_disp＝&quot;yes&quot; product_image_width=&quot;300&quot; product_image_height=&quot;300&quot; }}

&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;18-third-party-vendor-modules&quot;&gt;18. Third-party vendor modules&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We use several third-party vendor modules in our theme, we already have these modules in our theme package, so you don’t need to 
install theme, for usage, you can find guide for these modules in third-party vendor’s website, details is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;magento-2-advance-product-quick-view-and-ajax-cart&quot;&gt;Magento 2 Advance Product Quick View and Ajax Cart&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;https://www.weltpixel.com/advance-product-quick-view.html&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;swissuplabs-easy-tabs&quot;&gt;Swissuplabs Easy Tabs&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;http://docs.swissuplabs.com/m2/extensions/easytabs/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have chagne its backend menu a little bit, please go Backend -&amp;gt; Cattheme -&amp;gt; Swissup Easytabs -&amp;gt; EasyTabs to configure it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;magefan-blog&quot;&gt;Magefan Blog&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;https://magefan.com/magento2-blog-extension/&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><summary type="html">Thanks for purchase Rabel Magento2 responsive theme, this guide will help you to install and use this great theme in your site, if you have further questions please contact us at gizmocn@gmail.com</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Use Redis for Magento2 cache and session</title><link href="http://docs.cattheme.com/tutorial/magento2-redis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Use Redis for Magento2 cache and session" /><published>2017-06-16T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2017-06-16T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://docs.cattheme.com/tutorial/magento2-redis</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://docs.cattheme.com/tutorial/magento2-redis/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;install-redis&quot;&gt;Install Redis&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We use Ubuntu 16.04 as our main os, we will install redis now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prerequisites:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ sudo apt-get update
$ sudo apt-get install build-essential
$ sudo apt-get install tcl8.5
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Installing Redis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ wget http://download.redis.io/releases/redis-stable.tar.gz
$ tar xzf redis-stable.tar.gz
$ cd redis-stable
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Proceed to with the make command&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ make
$ make test
$ sudo make install
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once the program has been installed, Redis comes with a built in script that sets up Redis to run as a background daemon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To access the script move into the utils directory:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd utils
sudo ./install-server.sh
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the script runs, you can choose the default options by pressing enter. Once the script completes, the redis-server will be running in the background.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can start and stop redis with these commands (the number depends on the port you set during the installation. 6379 is the default port setting):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ sudo service redis_6379 start
$ sudo service redis_6379 stop      
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;securing-redis&quot;&gt;Securing Redis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By default, Redis server allows connections from anywhere which is insecure. Binding to localhost will restrict access to the server itself and is a good first step to protecting your server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open the Redis configuration file for editing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;sudo vi /etc/redis/6379.conf
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Locate this line and make sure it is uncommented (remove the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;#&lt;/code&gt; if it exists):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;bind 127.0.0.1
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is only a first step to securing your Redis instance, You may need more actions to protect your server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;test-the-redis-instance-functionality&quot;&gt;Test the Redis Instance Functionality&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To test that your service is functioning correctly, input:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ redis-cli ping
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should see:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;PONG
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;configure-magento-to-use-redis-for-default-and-page-caching&quot;&gt;Configure Magento to use Redis for default and page caching&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following is a sample configuration that causes Magento to use Redis for both the default cache (default array) and the full page cache (page_cache array).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add a configuration similar to the following to &lt;your Magento=&quot;&quot; install=&quot;&quot; dir=&quot;&quot;&gt;app/etc/env.php:&lt;/your&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;'cache' =&amp;gt;
array(
   'frontend' =&amp;gt;
   array(
      'default' =&amp;gt;
      array(
         'backend' =&amp;gt; 'Cm_Cache_Backend_Redis',
         'backend_options' =&amp;gt;
         array(
            'server' =&amp;gt; '127.0.0.1',
            'database' =&amp;gt; '0',
            'port' =&amp;gt; '6379'
            ),
    ),
    'page_cache' =&amp;gt;
    array(
      'backend' =&amp;gt; 'Cm_Cache_Backend_Redis',
      'backend_options' =&amp;gt;
       array(
         'server' =&amp;gt; '127.0.0.1',
         'port' =&amp;gt; '6379',
         'database' =&amp;gt; '1',
         'compress_data' =&amp;gt; '0'
       )
    )
  )
),
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;configure-magento-to-use-redis-for-session-storage&quot;&gt;Configure Magento to use Redis for session storage&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open &lt;your Magento=&quot;&quot; install=&quot;&quot; dir=&quot;&quot;&gt;app/etc/env.php, it may has session configure before, you can find below lines in env.php&lt;/your&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;  'session' =&amp;gt; 
  array (
    'save' =&amp;gt; 'files',
  ),
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Replace them by below configuration:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;'session' =&amp;gt; 
   array (
   'save' =&amp;gt; 'redis',
   'redis' =&amp;gt; 
      array (
	'host' =&amp;gt; '127.0.0.1',
	'port' =&amp;gt; '6379',
	'password' =&amp;gt; '',
	'timeout' =&amp;gt; '2.5',
	'persistent_identifier' =&amp;gt; '',
	'database' =&amp;gt; '2',
	'compression_threshold' =&amp;gt; '2048',
	'compression_library' =&amp;gt; 'gzip',
	'log_level' =&amp;gt; '1',
	'max_concurrency' =&amp;gt; '6',
	'break_after_frontend' =&amp;gt; '5',
	'break_after_adminhtml' =&amp;gt; '30',
	'first_lifetime' =&amp;gt; '600',
	'bot_first_lifetime' =&amp;gt; '60',
	'bot_lifetime' =&amp;gt; '7200',
	'disable_locking' =&amp;gt; '0',
	'min_lifetime' =&amp;gt; '60',
	'max_lifetime' =&amp;gt; '2592000'
    )
),
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;redis-monitor-command&quot;&gt;Redis monitor command&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a command prompt on the server on which Redis is running, enter:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ redis-cli monitor
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Refresh your storefront page and you’ll see output similar to the following.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you use Redis for session storage, you’ll see output similar to the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;1476824834.187250 [0 127.0.0.1:52353] &quot;select&quot; &quot;0&quot;
1476824834.187587 [0 127.0.0.1:52353] &quot;hmget&quot; &quot;sess_sgmeh2k3t7obl2tsot3h2ss0p1&quot; &quot;data&quot; &quot;writes&quot;
1476824834.187939 [0 127.0.0.1:52353] &quot;expire&quot; &quot;sess_sgmeh2k3t7obl2tsot3h2ss0p1&quot; &quot;1200&quot;
1476824834.257226 [0 127.0.0.1:52353] &quot;select&quot; &quot;0&quot;
1476824834.257239 [0 127.0.0.1:52353] &quot;hmset&quot; &quot;sess_sgmeh2k3t7obl2tsot3h2ss0p1&quot; &quot;data&quot; &quot;_session_validator_data|a:4:{s:11:\&quot;remote_addr\&quot;;s:12:\&quot;10.235.34.14\&quot;;s:8:\&quot;http_via\&quot;;s:0:\&quot;\&quot;;s:20:\&quot;http_x_forwarded_for\&quot;;s:0:\&quot;\&quot;;s:15:\&quot;http_user_agent\&quot;;s:115:\&quot;Mozilla/5.0 (Windows NT 10.0; Win64; x64) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Chrome/53.0.2785.143 Safari/537.36\&quot;;}_session_hosts|a:1:{s:12:\&quot;10.235.32.10\&quot;;b:1;}admin|a:0:{}default|a:2:{s:9:\&quot;_form_key\&quot;;s:16:\&quot;e331ugBN7vRjGMgk\&quot;;s:12:\&quot;visitor_data\&quot;;a:3:{s:13:\&quot;last_visit_at\&quot;;s:19:\&quot;2016-10-18 21:06:37\&quot;;s:10:\&quot;session_id\&quot;;s:26:\&quot;sgmeh2k3t7obl2tsot3h2ss0p1\&quot;;s:10:\&quot;visitor_id\&quot;;s:1:\&quot;9\&quot;;}}adminhtml|a:0:{}customer_base|a:1:{s:20:\&quot;customer_segment_ids\&quot;;a:1:{i:1;a:0:{}}}checkout|a:0:{}&quot; &quot;lock&quot; &quot;0&quot;

... more ...
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you use Redis for page caching, you’ll see output similar to the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;1476826133.810090 [0 127.0.0.1:52366] &quot;select&quot; &quot;1&quot;
1476826133.816293 [0 127.0.0.1:52367] &quot;select&quot; &quot;0&quot;
1476826133.817461 [0 127.0.0.1:52367] &quot;hget&quot; &quot;zc:k:ea6_GLOBAL__DICONFIG&quot; &quot;d&quot;
1476826133.829666 [0 127.0.0.1:52367] &quot;hget&quot; &quot;zc:k:ea6_DICONFIG049005964B465901F774DB9751971818&quot; &quot;d&quot;
1476826133.837854 [0 127.0.0.1:52367] &quot;hget&quot; &quot;zc:k:ea6_INTERCEPTION&quot; &quot;d&quot;
1476826133.868374 [0 127.0.0.1:52368] &quot;select&quot; &quot;1&quot;
1476826133.869011 [0 127.0.0.1:52369] &quot;select&quot; &quot;0&quot;
1476826133.869601 [0 127.0.0.1:52369] &quot;hget&quot; &quot;zc:k:ea6_DEFAULT_CONFIG_CACHE_DEFAULT__10__235__32__1080MAGENTO2&quot; &quot;d&quot;
1476826133.872317 [0 127.0.0.1:52369] &quot;hget&quot; &quot;zc:k:ea6_INITIAL_CONFIG&quot; &quot;d&quot;
1476826133.879267 [0 127.0.0.1:52369] &quot;hget&quot; &quot;zc:k:ea6_GLOBAL_PRIMARY_PLUGIN_LIST&quot; &quot;d&quot;
1476826133.883312 [0 127.0.0.1:52369] &quot;hget&quot; &quot;zc:k:ea6_GLOBAL__EVENT_CONFIG_CACHE&quot; &quot;d&quot;
1476826133.898431 [0 127.0.0.1:52369] &quot;hget&quot; &quot;zc:k:ea6_DB_PDO_MYSQL_DDL_STAGING_UPDATE_1&quot; &quot;d&quot;
1476826133.898794 [0 127.0.0.1:52369] &quot;hget&quot; &quot;zc:k:ea6_RESOLVED_STORES_D1BEFA03C79CA0B84ECC488DEA96BC68&quot; &quot;d&quot;
1476826133.905738 [0 127.0.0.1:52369] &quot;hget&quot; &quot;zc:k:ea6_DEFAULT_CONFIG_CACHE_STORE_DEFAULT_10__235__32__1080MAGENTO2&quot; &quot;d&quot;

... more ...
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;notice&quot;&gt;Notice&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the redis server is down, the Magneto2 site will crash also, to test it, stop redis server:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;sudo service redis_6379 stop
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then refresh Magento2 site, you will got below error message:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;CredisException: Connection to Redis failed after 2 failures.Last Error : (111) Connection refused in /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/colinmollenhour/credis/Client.php:448 Stack trace: #0 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/colinmollenhour/credis/Client.php(444): Credis_Client-&amp;gt;connect() #1 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/colinmollenhour/credis/Client.php(774): Credis_Client-&amp;gt;connect() #2 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/colinmollenhour/credis/Client.php(604): Credis_Client-&amp;gt;__call('select', Array) #3 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/colinmollenhour/cache-backend-redis/Cm/Cache/Backend/Redis.php(144): Credis_Client-&amp;gt;select(1) #4 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/magento/zendframework1/library/Zend/Cache.php(153): Cm_Cache_Backend_Redis-&amp;gt;__construct(Array) #5 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/magento/zendframework1/library/Zend/Cache.php(94): Zend_Cache::_makeBackend('Cm_Cache_Backen...', Array, true, true) #6 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/magento/framework/App/Cache/Frontend/Factory.php(155): Zend_Cache::factory('Magento\\Framewo...', 'Cm_Cache_Backen...', Array, Array, true, true, true) #7 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/magento/framework/App/Cache/Frontend/Pool.php(67): Magento\Framework\App\Cache\Frontend\Factory-&amp;gt;create(Array) #8 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/magento/framework/App/Cache/Frontend/Pool.php(146): Magento\Framework\App\Cache\Frontend\Pool-&amp;gt;_initialize() #9 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/magento/framework/App/Cache/Type/FrontendPool.php(84): Magento\Framework\App\Cache\Frontend\Pool-&amp;gt;get('default') #10 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/magento/framework/App/Cache/Type/Config.php(49): Magento\Framework\App\Cache\Type\FrontendPool-&amp;gt;get('config') #11 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/magento/framework/Cache/Frontend/Decorator/Bare.php(65): Magento\Framework\App\Cache\Type\Config-&amp;gt;_getFrontend() #12 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/magento/framework/App/ObjectManager/ConfigLoader.php(66): Magento\Framework\Cache\Frontend\Decorator\Bare-&amp;gt;load('global::DiConfi...') #13 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/magento/framework/App/ObjectManager/Environment/Developer.php(77): Magento\Framework\App\ObjectManager\ConfigLoader-&amp;gt;load('global') #14 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/magento/framework/App/ObjectManagerFactory.php(194): Magento\Framework\App\ObjectManager\Environment\Developer-&amp;gt;configureObjectManager(Object(Magento\Framework\Interception\ObjectManager\Config\Developer), Array) #15 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/magento/framework/App/Bootstrap.php(385): Magento\Framework\App\ObjectManagerFactory-&amp;gt;create(Array) #16 /var/www/html/magento2/vendor/magento/framework/App/Bootstrap.php(232): Magento\Framework\App\Bootstrap-&amp;gt;initObjectManager() #17 /var/www/html/magento2/index.php(38): Magento\Framework\App\Bootstrap-&amp;gt;createApplication('Magento\\Framewo...') #18 {main}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter below command to start redis server:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;sudo servcie redis_6379 start
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Refresh Magento2 site, it restore normal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reference&quot;&gt;Reference&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Magento DevDocs &lt;a href=&quot;http://devdocs.magento.com/guides/v2.0/config-guide/redis/config-redis.html&quot;&gt;DevDocs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Redis Official Site &lt;a href=&quot;https://redis.io/topics/quickstart&quot;&gt;redis.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;DigitalOcean &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.digitalocean.com/community/tutorials/how-to-install-and-use-redis&quot;&gt;redis installation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><summary type="html">Install Redis We use Ubuntu 16.04 as our main os, we will install redis now.</summary></entry></feed>